人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  小飯
翻譯  小暴徒
翻譯  丶Charl
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯  ET外星人
翻譯  珈美
翻譯  江湖人稱王姑娘
翻譯  沫沫
時間軸  小式
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第十一集
安德伍德總統夫婦今日返回路易斯安那州
President and Mrs. Underwood are back in Louisiana today,
為爭取獲得...
in an effort to pick up...
安德伍德今天來到拉斯維加斯
Underwood is in Las Vegas today,
與烹飪工會的領導人會面
meeting with leadership from the Culinary Union...
今天下午在查爾斯頓
...questions from undecided voters
回答游離選民的提問
in Charleston this afternoon,
這是今天三項安德伍德競選活動的第一項
the first of three events the Underwood campaign...
第一夫人今天在卡斯珀一市政廳集會上接受提問
The First Lady took questions at a town hall meeting in Casper today.
安德伍德夫婦6天就走了12個城市
That's 12 cities in half as many days for the Underwoods.
同時  他們仍在所有全國民調中
Meanwhile, they still trail Conway by 12
落后于康威12到14個百分點
to 14 points in every national poll.
這個差距并不小
That's a big gap to close...
博伊西的支持者比原計劃多等了總統兩小時
...supporters in Boise waited an extra two hours for the president...
總統在俄亥俄州的競選活動將會...
The president's whistle-stop tour of Ohio will...
你們就是能決定這一切的州之一
You're one of the states that will decide this!
今天下午在查爾斯頓
...took questions from undecided voters
回答游離選民的提問  這是今天三項...
in Charleston this afternoon, the first of three events...
請以波士頓式的熱情歡迎我們的下任總統
Please give a big Boston welcome to the next president...
對很多美國人來說  問題依然在于
For many Americans, the question remains,
兩位安德伍德進駐白宮
一個雙安德伍德式的白宮會是什么樣
what would an Underwood-Underwood White House look like?
兩位安德伍德進駐白宮
安德伍德夫婦二人都...
Both Underwoods have courted--
周一去亞利桑那州  內華達州和加州
So, Arizona, Nevada, and California on Monday,
周二去中西部地區的州
then the upper Midwest on Tuesday.
還不夠  康威去的州比我們多多了
It's not enough. Conway's hitting way more states than we are.
他又不是在任總統  比你有更多時間
Well, he's not a sitting president. He has more time than you do.
那我們就得擠出更多時間
Well, then we have to make more time.
我們必須到各地去  我們必須動...
We have to get out there. We've got to shake--
弗蘭西斯  你還好嗎
Francis, are you okay?
-我沒事  -坐一會兒吧
- I'm fine. - Sit down for a moment.
不不  我沒事  我沒事  我們繼續
No, no, I'm fine, I'm fine. Let's continue.
如果您想在加州多安排一場籌款活動
If you wanna add a fundraiser in California,
這個沒問題
we can make that happen.
好吧
Okay.
怎么樣
So?
我同意撒克遜醫生和醫療團隊的建議
I agree with Dr. Saxon and the medical team.
我們得把飛行次數減到一周一次
We should reduce air travel to once a week.
恐怕那不可能
I'm afraid that's not possible.
您想聽其他人的建議  先生  這就是
You wanted a second opinion, sir. You have it.
我不是想聽別人的建議  我是想聽不同的建議
I didn't want a second opinion. I wanted a different opinion.
飛機對您有傷害
Planes take a toll.
我們擔心突發器官排斥
We're concerned about a sudden organ rejection.
如果我不四處跑  我就無法贏得選舉
I can't win an election if I can't travel.
如果您住院了  也贏不了
You can't win if you're hospitalized.
謝謝你  醫生
Thank you, Doctor.
你留下來  康威去哪我就去哪  我會..
You stay here. I'll go wherever Conway goes, I'll just--
是我競選總統  我必須親自去
I'm on the top of the ticket. It has to be me.
我們不能無視醫生的建議  弗蘭西斯
We can't ignore the doctors, Francis.
宣傳是關鍵
It's the story we tell.
如果我留在這里  而康威到處奔走
If I stay here, Conway prances around the country,
標榜他的戰斗機飛行員形象  與此同時
playing up his fighter-pilot image, and meanwhile,
-我卻困在玫瑰園里  -我不能冒險失去你
- I'm stuck here in the Rose Garden-- - I won't risk losing you.
我們得明智點
Let's be smart about this.
-我得表現出力量  -那就去表現
- I need to project strength. - So project it.
空襲正在起效  先生
The air strikes are working, sir.
我們已經阻止了哈里發國進入幼發拉底河
We've stopped ICO's advance to the Euphrates.
只是延緩了進軍  沒有阻止
We've delayed the advance. We haven't stopped it.
你們的報告說他們在重新集結
Your own reports say they're regrouping.
我需要一次決定性打擊
I want a decisive blow,
抓人  領導人  傳達一個訊息
a face, the leadership, to send a message.
艾哈邁迪兄弟躲起來了
Uh, the Ahmadi brothers are in hiding.
我們不知道他們的藏身之處
We don't know their location.
你們的任務就是找到他們
Well, your task is to find them.
我們努力了  先生
We've tried, sir.
我們的特工毫無進展
Our assets hit a wall.
要徹底鏟除就得排遣特種部隊去那里
To root them out would require special forces on the ground.
這也不是不可以
That is a step I am willing to take.
我們沒有敘利亞的授權
We don't have authorization from the Syrians.
國務卿杜蘭特會擺平這件事
Secretary Durant will smooth that out.
我不會滿足于
I will not be satisfied
阻擋毒蛇的去路  先生們
by blocking the serpent's path, gentlemen.
我要砍掉它該死的腦袋
I wanna cut off its goddamn head.
敘利亞人會拒絕  到那時
The Syrians will say no, and when they do,
看看他們是否愿跟俄羅斯特種部隊合作
see if they'll work with the Russian special forces.
臟活讓俄羅斯人去干  我們坐收功勞
The Russians do the dirty work, we take all the credit.
佩特羅夫不會同意的
Petrov won't go for that.
還給他們幾個鉆井就會答應了
Well, he will if we give him back some of our drilling zones.
那需要國會的批準
Well, that'll take congressional approval.
道格正為此做準備
Doug's laying the groundwork now.
關于這件事你想聽聽我的意見
Are you interested in my opinion on this,
還是已經做好了決定
or has it already been decided?
我想迅速行動
I want to move fast,
所以除非你有更迅速的辦法
so unless you have a quicker option,
不然最好還是保留觀點吧
it's probably best you keep it to yourself.
-是  先生  -凱茜
- Yes, sir. - Cathy.
有什么問題嗎
Do we have a problem?
沒有  先生  我去和道格協調
No, sir. I'll coordinate with Doug.
被狗咬了以后  要么就把它干掉
After a dog's bitten you, you either put it to sleep,
要么就給它帶上口套
or you put a muzzle on it.
我暫時選擇...口套
I've chosen a muzzle... for now.
來的路上我一直在考慮
I was, uh, thinking on the way over here
我不想每次活動都發表同一篇講話
that I don't wanna do the same speech at every event.
我認為如果每次講話內容都不同
I really think we'll get more news coverage
能獲得更多的媒體關注
if I have a different speech every time.
莉安已經告訴我了
LeAnn already told me.
我做了一些修改
I've been working on some variations.
我覺得我們還得
I think, uh, we also need to
隨時對康威的言論作出回應
respond to what Conway is saying...at all times.
開始對他施加壓力
Start putting pressure on him.
賽斯的手下會把筆錄發給我
Seth's office is sending me transcripts.
《時代周刊》詢問可否做采訪
There was an interview query from Time,
一條什么紀念基金的語音留言
a voicemail about some memorial fund.
豪斯頓參議員來電確認周二會面的事
Senator Halston called about the meeting on Tuesday.
等等  那條語音留言
Wait. The voicemail.
留言的是勞拉·莫雷蒂
Uh, Laura Moretti,
安東尼·莫雷蒂紀念基金的
from the Anthony Moretti Memorial Fund.
-你之前好像...捐贈過  -幫我調出來
- I guess you... donated? - Cue that up for me.
按1號鍵就能聽了
Just press one when you're ready.
-過會兒再向我匯報  -好的
- I'll catch up with you in a little bit. - Okay.
您好  我是勞拉·莫雷蒂
Hi, this is Laura Moretti
留言給道格拉斯·斯坦普
leaving a message for Douglas Stamper.
我想親自跟您聯系
I just, uh... I wanted to reach out to you personally,
對您的慷慨捐贈表示感謝
to say thank you for the incredibly generous donation.
這是我們收到的最大一筆捐款
It's the biggest donation we've received.
遠超其他人
By a lot.
我不知道您是如何知道我們的
Uh, I don't know how you found out about us.
也許是因為總統的移植手術
Maybe because of the President's transplant.
但不論出于何種原因
But whatever the reason,
這對我和孩子們意義非凡
it means so much to us, to me and my children.
不論如何  我知道希望不大
Anyway, I... and I know this is a long shot,
但如果你有空一起喝杯咖啡的話
but if you're ever free for coffee,
我想當面謝謝您
I'd love to thank you in person.
沒空...也沒關系
No worries if... if you can't.
再次感謝您  斯坦普先生
Um, thanks again, Mr. Stamper.
安東尼·莫雷蒂紀念基金
您好  我是勞拉·莫雷蒂
Hi, uh, this is Laura Moretti
留言給道格拉斯·斯坦普
leaving a message for Douglas Stamper.
我想親自跟您聯系
I just, uh... I wanted to reach out to you personally,
對您的慷慨捐贈表示感謝
to say thank you for the incredibly generous donation.
這是我們收到的最大一筆捐款
It's the biggest donation we've received.
把稿子放到提詞器上還來得及嗎
Will there be enough time to get this up on the teleprompter?
主要是做了刪減
They're mostly cuts.
應該會很快  我這就去
Should be quick. I'll get it there now.
你改了什么
What did you change?
我刪去了有關愛的那一段
I took out the paragraph about love.
-那是最精彩的部分  -太軟弱了
- That's the best part. - It was too soft.
弗萊迪
燒烤餐館
這兒曾經是家燒烤店
This used to be a barbecue joint, here.
弗蘭克當總統前經常光顧
Frank came a lot before he was president.
怎么會變成這樣
What happened to it?
弗蘭克碰過的東西都是這下場
Same thing that happens to everything Frank touches.
-你介意嗎  -介意
- You mind? - I do mind.
我還沒答應什么
I haven't agreed to anything yet.
告訴我你知道的事
Tell me what you know.
我知道安德伍德在洗錢的事上撒謊了
I know Underwood lied about the money laundering.
我知道他見了拉尼根  雖然他否認了
I know he met with Lanagin when he said he didn't.
我知道艾德華·密查姆改動了出行記錄
I know Edward Meechum doctored travel records,
我還知道那一切你都參與了
and I know you were there for all of it.
然后塔斯克獲得赦免  你當上幕僚長
Then Tusk gets a pardon. You get Chief of Staff.
-明日黃花  -你為什么辭職
- Old news. - Why'd you quit the job?
我想回到私營企業
I wanted to go back in the private sector.
你才說過安德伍德碰過的東西都會被毀滅
You just said everything Underwood touches gets demolished.
我不喜歡他  那又怎么樣
I don't like the man. So what?
那你為什么在俄羅斯協議上又跟他合作
Why'd you team up with him again for the Russia deal?
我不需要喜歡一起做事的人
I don't have to like the people I work with.
而且  可以狠賺一筆
Plus, there was a fortune to be made.
問題是
See...
我認為你根本不在乎那個錢
I don't think you give a damn about the money.
這里面有其他事  你是不肯承認
There's a lot more to this you're not admitting.
但我認為你想承認
But I think you want to.
那么  你其實沒有任何實在的東西
So, truth is, you don't have anything solid.
我會把這事查個水落石出
I will get to the bottom of this story.
我們可以現在談  或者你可以回頭雇一堆律師
We can talk now, or you can wait till you have a team of lawyers
來跟我的事實核查員聊
talking to my fact checkers.
我曾被億萬富翁和總統威脅過
I've been threatened by billionaires and by presidents.
你以為一個失業記者能讓我緊張嗎
You think an out-of-work reporter makes me nervous?
我現在就可以給白宮打電話
I can call the White House right now,
讓他們知道你在調查這件事
let 'em know you're working on this story.
我約你就冒了這個險
That's a gamble I took asking to meet.
但是我賭
But my chips...
你好的一面占上風
are on the better part of you prevailing.
誰  做了什么  為什么  怎么做
The who... the what... the why, how...
別忽略了在哪里做
Don't ignore where.
我覺得轉一下會比較好
I think it'd be better if I turn it.
我覺得這一面稍微好點
I think... I think this side is a little better.
-是的  非常漂亮  -弗萊迪
- Yes, that's very nice. - Freddy.
-下午好  總統先生  -下午好
- Good afternoon, Mr. President. - Good afternoon.
海倫在教我做事呢
Helen is teaching me the ropes.
我們不打擾您了  先生
We'll leave you be, sir.
弗萊迪
Oh, Freddy?
你留一下吧  非常感謝
Why don't you stay back for a little bit? Thank you very much.
我馬上過去
I'll be right there.
好久不見
It's been a while.
他們  幾個月前把我調去了花房
Well, they, uh... moved me to the flower shop a few months ago.
在地下室
The basement.
所以你沒怎么見到我
That's probably why you haven't seen me around.
我絕對想不到  居然會喜歡做這個
Never would've guessed that, well, that this would be my thing.
看來老家伙還是能學點新把戲的
I guess you can teach an old dog new tricks.
-你孫子還好嗎  -他很好  很好
- How's your grandson? - He's good, good.
剛開始重新上學
Just started school again.
-他讀幾年級了  -六年級
- What grade is he in now? - Sixth grade.
慢慢長大了
Getting up there.
我真的得走了
I... I really should go.
有一大批秋季的花要送過來
We got a big, uh, shipment of autumn blooms in.
那下次再聊吧
Well, then another time, I guess, maybe.
弗蘭克
You know, Frank...
我很快就要走了
I'm gonna be leaving soon.
海倫的丈夫在喬治敦開了一家花店
Helen's husband opened up a flower shop in Georgetown.
他們想要我過去工作
They want me to work there.
你在這里不開心嗎  弗萊迪
Well, are you not happy here, Freddy?
該嘗試點新東西了
Time to try something new.
我能做點什么說服你留下來嗎
Well, is there anything I can do to convince you to stay?
加薪  調整工作時間
A raise? Better hours?
我很感激  但是我已經答應海倫了
I appreciate it, but I've already told Helen yes, and...
而我打算說到做到  那是我想做的
I plan on keeping my word on that. It's what I want.
我會想念你的  弗萊德
Well, I'm gonna miss you around, Freddy.
這里沒幾個人
There's not many people here...
Well, I guess there aren't that many people here
能讓我覺得那么自在
I'm all that comfortable with.
你知道你走之前應該做什么嗎
You know what you should do before you go?
你應該哪天晚上上來給我們做一頓肋排
You should come up here one night and cook us a rack of ribs.
我知道烤箱烤的肯定不如碳烤
Now, I realize oven-baked isn't nearly as good as the smoker,
但你怎么樣都能做得很美味
but you'd make 'em delicious, anyhow.
肋排  是嗎
Ribs? Really?
你想讓我給你做肋排吃
You want me to cook ribs for you.
對  就像以前那樣  有什么不對嗎
Well, sure, just like old times. What's wrong with that?
我只是仆人  對不對
I'm just the help, ain't I?
-不  不是這樣的  -我告訴你我遇見了好事
- No, that's not true. - I tell you I got something good going,
而你的第一反應不是
and your first thought ain't,
"弗萊迪  恭喜"
"Freddy, congratulations."
而是"給我做肋排"  對我的盛大歡送
It's "Make me ribs." And what's my big send-off?
-就是給你做肋排  -不
- I get to cook you ribs. - No.
你對這事太過敏感了
Look, you are being way oversensitive about this.
你誤解了我的意思
You're misinterpreting what I meant.
你說得對
You're right.
都是我的錯
It's all my fault.
-真不知克萊爾是怎么做到的  -你說什么
- I don't know how Claire does it. - What did you just say?
你也這么對她嗎  她也是收藏品之一
Is this how you treat her? She part of the collection, too?
我不知道你這怨氣從何而來
I don't know where all this is coming from,
但也太忘恩負義了
but it's extremely ungrateful,
想想我為你做了那么多
given all that I have done for you.
你為我做了什么  弗蘭克
What did you do for me, Frank?
這里是白宮
This is the White House.
你得叫我"總統先生"
You will call me "Mr. President"!
你就是個王八犢子
You're a motherfucker!
滾
Get out!
我的錯  我的錯
My bad, my bad.
你是個王八犢子  總統先生
You're a motherfucker, Mr. President!
安德伍德夫婦
康威州長一直聲稱
Governor Conway continues to say
我們在反恐上做得還不夠
we're not doing enough about terrorism,
但他忽視了哈里發國已得到遏制的事實
but he ignores the fact that ICO has been stopped in its tracks.
總統不眠不休地與國外敵人作斗爭
The president is working tirelessly to combat our enemies abroad,
康威州長的言論
and what Governor Conway lacks in his assessment...
忽略了總統數十年的經驗...
is the decades of experience the president brings...
你還應該繼續叫他"總統"嗎
Do you think you should keep calling him "The president"?
我想強調我們是競選搭檔
Well, I wanna emphasize that we're running mates,
而且莉安告訴我  婚姻角度并不成功
and LeAnn is telling me that the marriage angle isn't working.
別管什么調查
Screw the research.
人們想聽見真正的你  有血有肉的人
People want to hear the real you, a real person.
你在黨代會上向他們展示的就是真正的你
That's what you gave them at the convention.
抱歉
Sorry.
那情況完全不同
That was very different.
沒錯  的確不同  那時你是誠懇的
Exactly. It was very different. It was honest.
你不能只機械地回應他的話
And you don't want to just react to what he's saying.
你得拿出點東西來
You wanna offer something.
我跟弗蘭西斯一起競選了三十年
I have been campaigning with Francis for 30 years.
不能讓對手騎在你頭上
You don't ever let the opponent walk all over you.
如果受到攻擊  就得還擊
If you're getting attacked, you fight back.
可以  但用另一種方式還擊
Fine, but fight back in a different way.
這個人...他都是搞噱頭  很膚淺
This guy is... He's all spotlight and surface,
上雜志封面  玩推特  別玩他的游戲
and magazine covers and Twitter. Don't play his game.
壓根就別玩  擺脫游戲
Don't play the game at all, please. Get beyond the game.
我們早上再繼續做吧
You know what? Let's finish this in the morning, please.
抱歉  你說得對
I'm sorry. You're right.
關于這種事你的經驗比我多得多
You have a lot more experience in this kind of thing than I do.
-我應該聽你的  -不  我尊重你的反饋
- I should follow your lead. - No, I... I respect your feedback.
感謝你能表現得如此專業
Thank you for being so professional about everything.
-你真體貼  -不是體貼
- You've been very kind. - I'm not kind.
現實而已
Just realistic.
你寫的關于愛的那段讓我不舒服
That paragraph you wrote about love, it made me uncomfortable.
-說你愛弗蘭西斯  -我確實愛他
- Saying you love Francis? - I do love him.
那是什么讓你不舒服
Then what made you uncomfortable?
在你面前說出來
Saying it in front of you.
-好嗎  -好
- Yes? - Yeah.
-她怎么樣  -效果甚微
- How'd she do? - Very little effect.
-新聞上鋪天蓋地全是她  -白噪音
- She was all over the news. - White noise.
我們怎么深入人心
So how do we make it stick?
我能做的不多
Well, there's not much I can do.
我們給你權限了  我要得到更多結果
We gave you access. I need more than I'm getting.
你應該告訴我人們想要什么
You're supposed to tell me what people want.
人們不知道自己想聽爵士
People didn't know they wanted jazz
直到他們第一次聽到了爵士樂
until they heard it for the first time.
我能讓他們喜歡音樂  但我不能創作音樂
I can get them to like the music. I can't compose it.
你得給我點材料
Give me something I can work with.
我們可以把這事公諸于眾嗎
Is this something we could take public?
不  這是機密
No, it's classified.
但這太完美了  總統跟俄羅斯人勾結
But it's perfect, the president colluding with the Russians.
這個想法是可行的
The idea has merit.
俄羅斯人門路更廣
The Russians will have far more access,
而且也不會置美國軍隊于危險之中
and it doesn't put American troops in harm's way.
褒獎總統的政策不會讓我們得到選票
We don't get votes by praising the president's policy.
讓德雷爾在委員會審議中否決它
Let's have Dreyer block it in committee.
雖然我不喜歡總統最初處理哈里發國的方式
I don't like the way the president's handled ICO from the get-go,
但他這次的方法也許會有效
but his approach might work here.
那正是我要防止的
That's what I'm trying to prevent.
你想留哈里發國的領袖一命
So, you wanna keep the ICO leadership alive,
就為了我們能繼續拿這個說事
so we can stay on message?
只是拖到11月而已
Just until November,
等我們就職后就狠狠打擊他們
and then we'll hit 'em hard after inauguration.
我當初正是為這種扯淡事才辭職
This is the exact sort of BS I resigned over in the first place.
在那邊等我一下
I'll see you over there.
再有兩個月我們就能獲勝
Two months away from winning this thing.
一旦他獲得主動權  一旦他獲得一點勢頭
But if he gains the initiative, if he picks up any momentum,
都可能影響我們的勝算
that could put us in the margin of error.
我以為你不一樣
I thought you were different.
別胡思亂想  將軍
Don't get any ideas, General.
你登上我這艘船
You threw caution into the wind
就已把謹慎拋到九霄云外
when you got yourself on my ticket.
你再做一次  就顯得愚蠢了
You do it again, you start to look foolish.
你去跟德雷爾談談  讓他斃掉這項議案
You talk to Dreyer and 86 this bill.
來到威斯康星州怎能不來嘗嘗鮮
I couldn't come to Wisconsin without having a taste test.
海耶斯先生  我叫湯姆·漢默施密特
Mr. Hayes. My name's Tom Hammerschmidt.
我是一個自由記者
I'm a freelance reporter.
我想跟你談談
I was hoping I could talk to you for a moment.
我不跟記者談
I don't talk to reporters.
是關于總統的事
It's a story about the president.
你沒聽到我說什么嗎
Did you not hear me the first time?
我認為在你的燒烤店里...曾發生過一些事
I think things happened... in your barbecue place.
會面
Meetings.
你可能順耳聽到過什么
Things you might have overheard.
我覺得總統觸犯了法律
I think the president broke the law,
而且我覺得你知情
and I think you know about it.
跟我來  找個沒人能聽到的地方再聊
Come with me. Let's talk where no one can hear us.
-你帶錄音筆了嗎  -帶了
- So, uh, you bring a recorder? - Yeah.
好  我告訴你真相
All right. Here's the truth.
我不再為他工作了  我不再為他烤排骨了
I don't work for him no more. I don't serve him ribs no more.
我不想再跟他有任何關系
I don't want nothing to do with him no more.
即使我恨他  我也的確恨他
Even if I hated him, and I do hate him...
我也不會告密  對警察  對記者
I don't snitch. Not to cops, not to reporters.
對誰都不會
Not to anybody.
離我遠點
Leave me the fuck alone.
好了
Okay.
林肯和羅斯福都是共和黨的先進分子
Lincoln and Roosevelt were progressive Republicans.
-杰弗遜是一名有遠見的保守黨  -是的
- Jefferson was a visionary Conservative. - Yeah!
喬治·華盛頓是位強大的領袖
George Washington was a strong commander in chief.
威廉·康威擁有所有這些品質
William Conway embodies all these qualities.
我為背書他競選總統而驕傲
I proudly endorse his candidacy for president,
我也希望我們州的每個人都這么做
and I ask everyone in our great state to do the same.
歡迎未來的美國總統  威廉·康威
The next President of the United States, William Conway!
你們的支持讓我受寵若驚
I'm... I'm humbled by your endorsement,
我身后這些偉人遺留的貢獻也讓我自愧不如
and by the legacy of these great men behind me.
接任他們是一項艱巨的任務
Now, they all left very big shoes to fill.
知道誰完全沒有接任的資格嗎
You know who hasn't come even close to filling them?
弗蘭克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
我該離開
I should go.
我們降落之后
Once we land.
我就飛回東海岸
I'll get a flight back to the East Coast.
-湯姆...  -你不用多說了
- Tom... - You don't have to say anything.
有人向房子扔雞蛋
We've had eggs thrown at the house.
番茄  牛糞  什么都有
Tomatoes, cow dung. You name it.
南達科他州十分支持康威
South Dakota's big Conway country.
我們一生都住在這兒  也在這兒養育后代
We've been here all our lives. We raised our son here.
從未遇到過這種情況
It's just beyond our experience.
這些人都是我們的鄰居
All these folks are our neighbors.
可我一把標志豎起來
But once I put that sign up...
康威州長是退伍軍人  而且有孩子
Governor Conway is a veteran. He has children.
為什么選我們  而不是他
Why us and not him?
當我們看到你們兩個在黨代會
When we saw you two at the convention...
我說不清  看上去真像對兒好搭檔
I don't know. It just seemed like a real partnership.
愛  深沉  堅定的愛
Love. Deep, unwavering love.
感謝你們提醒我
I wanna thank you for reminding me
那種愛有多重要
how important that kind of love is.
它真的很重要  我們容易忙于競選
Because it is. It's easy to get caught up in the campaign
而忘記弗蘭西斯和我是怎樣走到這一步的
and to forget how Francis and I got here in the first place,
記得我們不僅是總統和第一夫人
to remember that we're not just President and First Lady,
或丈夫和妻子
or husband and wife.
我們是搭檔
We're partners.
我們決定要一起解決所有事
We have made a choice to tackle everything together.
我們超越了美麗和完美
We go beyond what's pretty and perfect,
超越了恐懼  困難和未知
beyond what's scary, difficult and unknown.
我們不僅是候選人名單上的搭檔
We're not just partners on the ticket.
我們也是生活中的搭檔
We're partners in life.
總統先生
Mr. President.
眾議院情報委員會里
You have someone on the inside of
有人給你
the House Intelligence Committee
提供機密信息
feeding you classified information.
我是在任州長
I'm a sitting governor.
獲得信息沒什么錯
There's nothing wrong with staying informed.
所有共和黨人都在反對俄羅斯的介入
Every Republican is against the Russians being involved.
你是在干預國家安全
You are interfering with national security.
我沒擺布任何人
I haven't influenced a single member.
那是因為你讓布洛哈特這么做
Oh, that's because you're having Brockhart do it.
如果將軍提供專業建議
If the general chooses to share his expertise with them,
他們當然愿意聽
they're well served by it.
你每天要說50次我們得摧毀哈里發國
Fifty times a day, you say we should destroy ICO,
現在又故意阻止我們那么做
and now you're deliberately preventing us from doing it.
你6個月前就可以摧毀他們了
You could've destroyed them six months ago,
所以不要把這賴在我...
so don't lay that at my...
我不怪你裝相  州長
I don't blame you for being a fraud, Governor.
我們都偶爾要偽善一下
I mean, we all have to be hypocrites, every now and then.
但如果你阻止  我就得派美國軍隊
But if you block this, I'll send American troops in instead.
你不會派美國人過去的  敘利亞不會同意的
You won't send Americans. Syria won't allow it.
我不在乎敘利亞會不會同意
I don't care what Syria will allow.
但你難道不希望讓俄羅斯人去冒險
But wouldn't you rather have it be Russians in harm's way,
而不是美國同胞士兵嗎
than your fellow American soldiers?
如果有人犧牲  那將是你一手造成的
If anyone gets killed, that's going to be blood on your hands.
你想讓我叫共和黨人同意
You want me to tell the Republicans to... get on board.
或讓將軍去做
Or have the general do it.
把政治放在一邊  做正確的事
Put politics aside and do the right thing.
你真以為你這通電話
Did you really think you'd be able to convince me
能說服我嗎  總統先生
by making this call, Mr. President?
我領先兩位數  我的說法能博取支持
I'm ahead by double digits. I got a message that's working.
你有麻煩  就訴諸于我的責任感
You're on your heels, and you're asking me to help you
想讓我幫你
by appealing to my sense of duty?
就連你都信了我的說辭
I've even got you sold on my message.
你不該太相信電視上的東西
Well, you shouldn't believe everything you see on TV.
州長掛電話了  總統先生
The governor has ended the call, Mr. President.
我們走
Let's go.
我們要出動自家的地面部隊
We're gonna go forward with our own ground operation.
我去通知參聯會  先生  還有件事
I'll inform the Joint Chiefs. Sir, there's another thing.
情報委員會
The Intelligence Committee...
如果康威在內部有人
If Conway has someone on the inside--
你是擔心對監控的監督
You're worried about oversight on surveillance.
人們對此更加關注了
There's increased attention.
如果他們打探  發現了麥卡倫做的事
They dig around, find out what Macallan's up to...
我們不是無懈可擊嗎
Yeah, but I thought we were airtight.
莉安那么說  但還是...
Leann says we are, but still...
最保險的就是了結此事
The safest thing would be to end it.
克萊爾·安德伍德這兩天一直在活動
Claire Underwood's been on the move the past two days,
走訪康威州長辦過活動的每一個州
showing up in every state Governor Conway's held events.
總統卻一直缺席
Absent from the trail has been the President.
引用新聞發言人賽斯·格雷森的原話
Press Secretary Seth Grayson said, quote,
"總統目前正在處理
"The President is attending to the business of government
政府事務"
for the time being," end quote.
但他沒有表明
But he neglected to say
總統何時會繼續競選
when the President would resume campaigning,
目前競選網站上
and there are no upcoming events
也沒有列出近期活動信息
currently listed on the campaign website,
這讓人推測總統缺席的真正原因
leading some to speculate that the real reason for his absence
可能是身體問題
may be health-related.
總統接受肝臟移植已經過去六個月了
It's been six months since the President received a liver transplant.
雖然他可以繼續正常...
Although he was able to resume normal...
-你的眼睛怎么了  -弗萊迪·海耶斯干的
- What happened to your eye? - Freddy Hayes.
那他什么都沒說了
So I assume he didn't talk.
我需要一個切入點  丹頓先生
I need a way in here, Mr.Danton.
我已經盡力幫你了
I've helped you as much as I can.
我知道你不會公開作證
I know you won't go on record.
我甚至不要求你作為背景出現
I'm not even asking to put you on background.
我只想知道我是接近還是偏離
All I'm looking for is whether I'm warm or cold.
這是什么啤酒
What kind of beer is that?
貯藏啤酒  微釀的...我不知道名字
A lager. Some microbrew they had, um... I don't know the name.
我能嘗嘗嗎
Mind if I try it?
請便
Go ahead.
好喝
It's good.
我年少時候玩過一個喝酒游戲
Used to play a drinking game when I was a teenager...
叫"我從來沒有過"
called Never Have I Ever.
-知道那游戲嗎  -有過那個經歷就喝
- You know that game? - You drink when you have.
就是那個
That's the one.
或者如果總統有過
Or if the President has.
被特別檢察官調查的時候
Never have I ever perjured myself
我從來沒有做過偽證
when investigated by a special prosecutor.
我從來沒有和雷蒙德·塔斯克達成過協議
Never have I ever struck a deal with Raymond Tusk...
讓他做偽證換取赦免
to perjure himself in exchange for a pardon.
我從來沒有密謀彈劾過總統
Never have I ever conspired to impeach a President
好讓我自己當上總統
so I could become President myself.
我們得再叫點酒了
We're gonna need more beer.
-第一夫人在1號線上  先生  -謝謝
- The First Lady is on line one, sir. - Thank you.
克萊爾
Claire.
道格給我打電話說我們要派出自己的軍隊
Doug called me about sending in our own troops.
要么派出要么無所行動  康威不肯讓步
Well, it was that, or sit on our hands. Conway wouldn't budge.
凱茜怎么說
And what does Cathy say?
我更想知道你的想法
I'm more interested in hearing what you think.
我認為...采取點行動總比什么都不做強
Well, I think... doing something is better than doing nothing.
活動怎么樣了
How are the events going?
說不好  做了好多場  都分不清了
It's hard to tell. I've done so many, it's all a blur.
今晚只剩一場訪談了
There's only one interview left tonight,
今天就結束了
and then we're done for the day,
但是...明天有七場
but then there's, uh... seven events tomorrow.
你還好吧
How are you holding up?
我想告訴你湯姆不再為選舉工作了
I called to tell you Tom's not working on the campaign anymore.
-他辭職了  -不是
- Did he quit? - No.
怎么回事
What happened?
我們倆決定這樣最好
We both decided it was for the best.
我們不用擔心他  弗蘭西斯
We don't have to worry about him, Francis.
你聽起來很累
You sound tired.
今晚好好睡一覺吧
Make sure you get a full night's sleep tonight.
-弗蘭西斯  -怎么了
- Francis? - Yes?
沒事
Nothing.
-明天見  -好的  明天見
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay, tomorrow.
-你確定安德伍德知道  -但沃克不知道
- You're certain Underwood knew? - And Walker didn't.
丹頓會不會有什么企圖
Could Danton have some agenda on this?
他沒有理由撒謊
He has no reason to lie.
除了他還有誰能證實
Who's corroborated, besides him?
沒有了  所以我才來這兒
No one. That's why I'm here.
我需要制度支持  律師  調查...
I need institutional support. Legal, research...
還有不會被我的狗干擾的辦公地點
a place to work where my dog won't bark at me.
如果能搞定這篇報道  你想做什么都行
If you crack this story, you can do anything you want.
-我還可以讓你再當上主編  -我不要
- I'll even make you managing editor again. - I don't want that.
我想要的是...絕對自主權
What I do want... is absolute autonomy.
組建自己的團隊  小規模
I build my team, I keep it small,
并且只向你匯報
and I answer only to you.
-人身安全呢  -這只是不走運
- How about security? - Oh, this was just some bad luck.
我已經失去兩名記者了  湯姆
I've lost two reporters, Tom.
拜托  瑪格麗特
Oh, come on, Margaret.
安德伍德或許是個壞蛋  但他不會殺人
Underwood may be a crook, but he's not a killer.
我也這么看  但我不想冒險
I don't think so either, but I don't wanna take any chances.
你把我要的人找來就好
You just get me the staff I need.
文章一旦發表  就沒人能動我了
Once this article comes out, I'm untouchable.
白宮要想揮拳頭  就讓律師出面
When the White House starts throwing punches... lawyer up.
因為他只能沖著《先驅報》  不能沖我來
'Cause he's gonna throw 'em at the Herald, not me.
我以前的愛好
Hobby I used to have.
莽原之役
The Battle of the Wilderness.
美國內戰戰役  1864年5月5日至7日
我花了幾個月  造了一個模型
I spent months building a model of it.
之后想再造一個  卻沒有完成
Started another one, but never finished it.
-為什么  -我成了總統
- Why not? - I became president.
時間總不夠
Never enough time.
克萊爾知道你叫我過來嗎
Does Claire know you asked me here?
不知道
No.
你們不只是玩玩而已吧
It was more than just a fling, wasn't it?
-她怎么說的  -我沒問
- How did she describe it? - I didn't ask.
我就不詳述細節了
Well, I'm not gonna go into details.
那樣對你太失敬
I respect you too much for that.
你們倆從德州回來時
When you two came back from Texas...
我就有所感覺
I had a feeling.
她說  你逗她母親笑了
She says... you made her mother laugh.
是啊  看來她挺喜歡我
Yeah, I guess she took a liking to me.
上帝  30年來  我從沒見那女人笑過
Christ, I haven't seen that woman laugh in 30 years.
因為我不是威脅
I'm just not a threat.
我不做評判  而是接受了她
Just someone who didn't judge, accepted her.
你把克萊爾也逗笑了嗎
Do you make Claire laugh?
我們有共鳴
We have a connection.
是的  我也讓她笑了
Yeah... I make her laugh.
讓她有被渴望的感覺
I make her feel desired.
我覺得她愿意讓我看到她脆弱的一面
I think she feels comfortable being vulnerable around me.
我得說  你沒生氣  讓我有些驚訝
I have to say, I'm a bit surprised you're not upset.
-生氣有什么好處  -我很欽佩  弗蘭克
- What would that achieve? - I admire that, Frank.
我昨天對一個老朋友發火了
I got angry with an old friend yesterday
因為他叫我弗蘭克  而不是總統先生
for calling me "Frank" Instead of "Mr. President."
就因為直呼你的名字嗎
Just for using your name?
我想不是因為名字
It wasn't the name, I suppose.
而是因為他要離開我了
It's the fact that he's leaving me.
-怎么離開你  -換工作了
- Leaving you how? - New job.
-他本來為你工作嗎  -就在白宮
- He worked for you? - Here in the White House.
下屬要和上司做朋友不容易
It's tough for employees to be your friends.
所以我決定做個了結
That's why I decided to end it.
-是你要走的  -這樣她就不用開口了
- You decided to leave. - So that she wouldn't have to ask me to.
那你的書呢
And what about your book?
我決不會那樣背叛她
I would never betray her like that.
謝謝你  湯姆
Thank you, Tom.
-我送你出去  -我自己走就好
- I'll walk you out. - I know my way out.
不過謝了
But thanks.
保重  弗蘭克
Take care, Frank.
三支隊伍  北面  東面  西面
Three teams. North, east, and west.
我們形成三角攻勢  向中心進發
We'll triangulate and advance on the center.
每支隊伍都將有一名外勤特工
Each team will have a field agent
與當地人員一同尋找艾哈邁迪兄弟
working with local assets to locate the Ahmadis.
這是行政命令  先生
Here's the executive order, sir.
您希望直接擊斃還是活捉
Do you have a preference? Dead or alive?
如果他們能提供情報  就活捉
Alive, if we can get intelligence out of 'em.
-謝謝  先生  -謝謝  先生
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
記住  你是在向我匯報
You're officially briefing me
關于哈里發國的監控行動
on ICO-related surveillance activities.
你從未與總統見面或談話
You never saw or spoke to the President.
走這邊
This way.
麥卡倫先生
Mr. Macallan.
-總統先生  -總統在他的宅邸
- Mr. President. - The President's in his residence...
不在這里
not here.
安全問題  我們有些擔憂
Security. We have concerns.
康威在眾議院情報委員會里有人
Conway has people on House Intelligence.
我把一切都掩蓋好了
I've got everything masked.
監控哈里發國和給競選用的算法完全相同
The algorithms for ICO and the campaign are identical.
只是輸入的變量不一樣而已
It's just a matter of what variables you input.
說通俗點
Give me English.
一只勺子  我可以用來攪拌咖啡
One spoon. I can use it to stir my coffee...
用來喝湯
to eat soup...
或是加熱海洛因
to boil heroin.
他們只能看見勺子  看不見我用它做什么
All they see is the spoon, not what I do with it.
或者我們干脆讓勺子消失
Or we could just get rid of the spoon.
關停嗎  那太可惜了
Shut it down? Well, that would be a shame,
特別是在昨天之后
especially after yesterday.
-昨天發生了什么  -超越了發生
- What happened yesterday? - Beyond happened.
"超越"
"Beyond"?
你太太在南達科塔州說的話
What your wife said in South Dakota.
"超越美麗和完美"
"Beyond what's pretty and perfect."
擺脫習俗  過往
Liberation from convention, from the past.
超越表面  超越空談  超越競選
Beyond surface, beyond bullshit, beyond the election.
-超越婚姻  -正是
- Beyond marriage. - Yes, exactly.
你們不僅是夫妻  不僅是競選搭檔
You're not just husband and wife. You're not just running mates.
你們兩者都是  卻不止于此
You're both and more.
你們代表了一種可能
You're what's possible.
康維夫婦是夢幻偶像
The Conways are everything everyone wants to be.
但你們才是理想境界
You're everything everyone wants to become.
總統遭到了槍擊  做了肝臟移植
The President has been shot. He's had a liver transplant.
我相信匹茲堡的所有人都在想
And I'm sure everyone here in Pittsburgh is wondering,
如果他死了怎么辦
what happens if he dies?
無意冒犯  不過...
Not to be indelicate, but...
如果我成了總統嗎
What if I became president?
這很合理
And that's fair.
我黨選擇我  因為他們看到的是
Our party chose me because they saw
一個團隊不可分割的一半
one half of an indivisible team.
無條件的支持
Unconditional support.
攜手共進多年的兩人
Two people working together for years.
相互支撐是一回事
Supporting each other is one thing.
經驗是另一回事
Experience is another.
你的經驗很少
You have very little.
從你的戒指看得出你結婚了
I can see from your ring that you're married.
是的  18年了
Yes. Eighteen years.
那么你知道什么是真正的搭檔
So you know what real partnership is.
我們一起走過了30年
We have 30 years under our belts.
相互學習  相互建議  這就是經驗
Learning from and advising each other? I'd call that experience.
好  你們有堅實的婚姻
Okay, so you've got a strong marriage,
但說到你的資歷
but in terms of your qualifications--
我想說的是
What... what I'm saying is
我們要超越夫妻關系來看
that we need to get beyond husband and wife.
我們要站在團隊的角度看
We need to look at the team.
弗蘭西斯在國會和白宮干過
Francis has served in Congress, in the White House.
我經營過大型非盈利機構  做過大使
I've run a major nonprofit. I served as ambassador.
我們曾一起通過立法  制定政策
We have passed legislation, developed policy.
一切都是我們一起做的  每一步都是
We've done all of that together, every step of the way.
所以我們一起競選是很自然的事
So it's natural that we would run together.
而且我比誰都了解弗蘭西斯
And I know Francis better than anyone.
所以  回答你的問題  如果他死了
So, if he died, to answer your question,
還有誰比我更適合實現他的美國計劃呢
who better to carry out his plan for America?
操縱
Manipulation.
欺騙
Deception.
腐敗
Corruption.
這就構成濫用職權和觸犯法律了
That translates to abuse of power and breaking the law.
我們知道是這樣  但我們需要確證
We know it's true, but we need corroboration.
要有公開證人  所有事實經過調查
People on record, every fact researched
并且反復核實
and checked and double-checked.
一切討論內容不得外傳
Nothing we discuss leaves this room.
不能透露給朋友  家人
Not your friends, not your family,
或是門外那50個
not the 50 reporters outside that door
想知道我們在這里干什么的記者
who wanna know what we're doing in here.
一旦白宮對我們做的事有一絲察覺
The second the White House gets wind of what we're doing...
他們就會設法讓這個報道
they start to make this story...
消失
disappear.
你在電臺訪問中的表現太出彩了
The radio interview you did was spectacular.
感覺不錯
It felt good.
我覺得我們終于找到發力點了
I feel like we're finally tapping into something.
你在南達科塔那對夫婦那里說的話
Was it Tom, what you said in South Dakota,
是湯姆想的嗎
with the couple?
我看過視頻了
I saw a videotape of it.
核心是的  然后...
The core of it, yes. And then...
我自己編了一些
I sort of made it my own.
他應該留下
He should stay on.
-不  -不是作為你的講稿撰稿人
- No. - Not as your speechwriter.
我的意思是  對外人來說
Well, I mean, yes, to the rest of the world,
他還是我們的講稿撰稿人
he can be our speechwriter.
但這不是他應該留下來的原因
But that's not why he should stay on.
他應該留下來  因為...
He should stay on because...
他能給你我給不了的東西
he can give you things that I can't.
克萊爾  我們一直是個強大的團隊
Look, Claire, we've been a great team.
但是一個人...
But one person...
一個人終究不能給另一個人一切
one person cannot give everything to another person.
我不能和你一起旅行
I can't travel with you.
不能在夜里給你溫暖
I don't keep you warm at night.
也不能像他那樣看待你
I don't see you the way he sees you.
這事不由我允許  但是...
It-- Look, it's not my permission to give, but...
你會做對自己正確的事
you'll do what's right for you.
但我想讓你知道  如果你想...
But I want you to know, if you want it...
我知道你會小心的...
I know you'll be careful...
我不介意
and I'll be fine.
如果我們要超越婚姻  那就超越吧
I mean, if we're gonna go beyond marriage, let's go beyond it.
您有三條已存留言
You have three saved messages.
第一條信息  9月8日
Message one. September 8th--
您好  我是勞拉·莫雷蒂  留言給道格拉斯...
Hi, uh, this is Laura Moretti leaving a message for Douglas--
保存留言請按8
To save this message, press eight.
回撥請按5
To call back, press five.
如
To-- -
抱歉  我的保姆到晚了...
I'm sorry. Uh, my sitter was late, and, um...
-路上堵車  -放松
- and then there was traffic, so-- - Just relax.
沒關系
It's fine.
很高興能見到您本人
It's so nice to meet you in person.
給
Here.
我也不知道為什么買了花  我大概...
I don't know why I got them. I guess I, uh...
-總之  -真美  謝謝
- Anyway. - No, they're lovely. Thank you.
還有...再次感謝您...給我們捐款
And, uh... and thank you again... for that donation.
我無法表達這對我們多重要
I just... I can't tell you how much it means--
在語音留言里  還有之前通話時
You already thanked me on your voice message
你已經謝過我了
and when we talked on the phone.
不用再感謝了
You don't need to thank me anymore.
好  不說謝謝了
Okay, no more thanks.
希望這個地方還行
I hope this place is okay.
不是什么高檔餐廳  但我常來
It's nothing fancy, but I come here a lot.
我喜歡  挺有個性的地方
I like it. It has a lot of character.
東尼喜歡這種小餐館
Tony liked greasy spoons like this.
他以前每周日下午
He used to take the kids to,
都帶孩子們去賓士紅辣碗餐館
Ben's Chili Bowl every Sunday afternoon
買熱狗給他們吃
and get them hot dogs.
抱歉
Sorry.
沒事
Don't be.
我也許不該談我丈夫
I probably just shouldn't talk about my husband.
我還是會控制不住情緒
I still get emotional.
你可以談...如果你想談的話
You can... if you want to.
哪怕我哭
Even if I cry?
我想多了解他
I wanna know more about him.
能關一下門嗎
Will you close the doors, please?
他在哪
Where is he?
我兩天來了這里兩次
Twice in two days I've been here.
我知道
I know.
為什么叫我來
So, why am I here now?
我希望你回來
I want you back.
我也是
I want you back, too.
但是...
But...
他理解
He understands.
■
從美國首位第一夫人瑪莎·華盛頓
到現在住在白宮的米歇爾·奧巴馬
美國歷史上出現過很多杰出的第一夫人
她們不僅能在政務上輔佐自己的丈夫
成為總統的諍友良伴
更有幾位還憑借非凡的才能和魅力
在美國歷史上留下了自己的印記
■
無論是比爾·克林頓兩番問鼎白宮  還是希拉里·克林頓兩次參選總統
他們一直都攜手作戰  既是夫妻  也是戰友
在希拉里08年失敗的總統競選  和目前正在進行的大選中
她都將比爾·克林頓作為一件終極武器
因為比爾雖然離任多年  但在美國選民中一直有著非常高的支持率
但終極武器使用不當  也會事倍功半
比如在08年的選舉中
媒體就認為比爾·克林頓過度攻擊奧巴馬  招致黑人選民反感
這對希拉里的失敗要負有一定責任
在目前正在進行的選舉中  比爾·克林頓也十分賣力
希拉里在初選初期凱歌高奏  比爾功不可沒
而在生活中  由于希拉里離開白宮后  有了自己的事業  同比爾聚少離多
很多人認為  兩人更像是政治盟友
希拉里對比爾繼續拈花惹草的緋聞并不在意